One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
T-T-They've all assembled!
The participants in the Colosseum's final match have finally assembled!
The four block winners and Mr. Diamante.
Donquixote Family Top Commander
Diamante ♦
The prize that will be given to one of these winners is...
Considered one of the strongest Devil Fruits, the Logia type Flame Fruit!
Diamante and Pica
It's gonna be mine.
If he's not Lucy, then who is he?
Don't start the match!
Remove Rebecca from the ring!
Block D needs a redo!
It seems there's some trouble.
As if we'll accept that ridiculous result, Rebecca!
There's no way we'd lose to a brat like you!
We'll finish the match right now!
That's right, kill her!
Hey, get out of the way.
What a bunch of sore losers.
What's done is done.
Don't mess with my performance!
What are you up to?!
Now, aim carefully.
You think we're bulls?!
Don't underestimate us!
It may be flapping in the wind, but this cape is made of steel.
I'm a Flag man who ate the Ripple Fruit.
I can turn my body and everything I touch into fluttering material.
Lock!
Corrida Glaive!
It would be best if you retreated now.
We've let loose some Fighting Fish that are suitable for the finals.
They're very sensitive to the smell of blood.
It's fly-
Did you guys see that?
That Fighting Fish's charge?
They're heinous animals that will attack even the participants in the ring.
They've got the most twisted personalities.
They're on a completely different level to the Fighting Fish in the preliminary rounds.
The bosses of each school of Flying Fish!
And on the back of just one of them, this tournament's prize,
the Flame Fruit is tied to it!
The rules of the finals are simple.
The last one standing, who manages to steal the Fruit, wins!
Now, the final battle,
a battle royale of five people, including our hero Diamante, is about to begin!
A scramble for the Devil Fruit!
A death match with the Fighting Fish!
Who will win the Flame Fruit?!
Now,
for...
the starting gong!
We're finally here.
The Royal Palace Lower Section
In front of the Rampart Tower
Is that the entrance to the palace?
That's just the palace's lower column.
The entrance to the rampart tower.
There's a secret entrance to the Rampart Tower as well. Let's go that way.
Be careful not to get discovered by the guards.
If we make a fuss and the commanders find out, we won't be able to move freely.
Especially if we're found by Pica, we'll never reach Doflamingo.
Hm? Where's Luffy-dono?
Um... there!
Rubber...
What the hell is that carp?!
Giant...
What's with this carp?!
Is it a pufferfish?
Pistol!
What the hell are you doing?!
It's open.
Don't give me that!
No way.
You dunce!
No choice.
Let's go, at this point, it's faster to go through the front gate.
Can I take this off already?
Do whatever you want!
Now, now...
That's...
This is a report from the entrance of the Rampart Tower!
There's an intruder. It's Straw Hat Luffy!
The Fighting Fish attacks, but Lucy dodges it effortlessly!
What great movement!
What are they on about?
Is he really the intruder?
It's true.
He destroyed the gate.
But it can't be him.
Straw Hat is fighting in the Colosseum under the name Lucy right now.
This is Rampart Tower B-2, in front of the dining hall!
There's no doubt about it, the intruders are Straw Hat Luffy,
the Pirate Hunter, Zoro,
and V-Violet-sama!
Then who the hell is the guy in the colosseum right now?!
Just what is going on?!
Palace Commerce Port
Lift between the
Commerce Port and Palace
Currently moving up
Doflamingo Family
(♦Diamante Army)
Lao G
Captain!
Damn you!
Kabu-san!
What just happened?
Damn fools.
What happened, you ask?
Since you want to know so much, I shall tell you.
I didn't expect a commander be on standby in this lift.
I was given an order to protect the Toys' House,
so I got on the lift to go down and wait in ambush at the underground trading port.
But I got on it a second time.
In other words...
G, for I Got on the wrong lift!
I won't let you go to the palace, intruders.
No... You will let us pass!
Royal Palace Rampart
Tower B-1
Straw Hat Luffy has entered Rampart Tower B-1!
Which way?
Left.
There's nobody here. Just you wait, Mingo!
The guards can't keep up with us.
What is that?!
A stone monster?!
Oh no! It's Pica!
It's huge! What is that thing?!
Be careful! He's one of the Family's top officers!
That stone monster?
Pica ate the Stone Fruit and gained the power to merge with stone!
So he's not just a stone man.
He can merge with any stone he touches.
Meaning, that since this palace is made of stone,
he can control the entire thing!
The walls!
Corrida Colosseum
There's another bloodthirsty Fighting Fish jumping out!
It's charging at Burgess!
Wave Motion...
Elbow!
The Colosseum is shaking!
It blasted a massive hole in the spectator's seats!
Burgess' powerful Wave Motion Elbow!
The upstart pirate, Blackbeard and the ten Fleet Captains that support him.
This is one of them, Jesus Burgess.
That bastard!
Don't involve the audience!
What a destructive power!
Oh, another Fighting Fish has appeared.
It's charging toward the right.
This is...
It's here, it's here, it's here!
It's shown up! The one with the Devil Fruit on its back, Fighting Fish 01!
There it is.
Is it after Bartolomeo?!
Or so we thought, before it changed directions!
Just who is it after?
Who is Fighting Fish 01 after?!
Ah, it's going after Rebecca!
I'll at least cut those chains.
Alright, I've got ya!
As if I'd let you!
You want a fight?
Alright! Lucy and Diamante are facing off!
Straw Hat!
Now you're up against me!
I'll be the one to take the Flame Fruit!
I'll take you both down at once.
Burgess has taken his stance again!
Run!
It's coming again!
Sly bastard, standing behind me!
Not gonna dodge, huh, Lucy?
Wave Motion...
Dragon's Claw!
Lucy!
Oh my, Burgess' armor has been shattered!
A-As expected of my Grand Senpai.
I guess you won't just give me the Flame Fruit.
His fighting style is different.
Is this guy really Straw Hat?
Underground Commerce Port
Usopp's group
Current Location
Toys keep coming out.
This is clear proof that Sugar is in the Commanders' Tower.
What are those tubes for?
Right in the middle of that tower lies the commanders' private lift.
As for the pipes extending all around it,
big humans and broken toys are sent in through those.
There are numerous entrances to the scrapyard all throughout Dressrosa,
Get dropped into any one of them,
and you'll reach the scrapyard, located right below the Officers' Tower.
I'm fed up with this! First a mountain of garbage, now this?
Where am I?
And what is this slimy stuff?
I thought it was weird that they sent me to the medical room when I wasn't injured.
It's not "slimy stuff"! It's "Sticky"!
Get back! Who the hell are you?!
This is the Officers' Tower.
Inside the Officers' Tower
But this factory where toys are born...
also has another name.
Sugar! What is that other name?
The Officers'' Tower.
No!
Oh, snot came out! My nose is running!
Gross. Die.
I won't die! I won't listen to a little kid like you!
Donquixote Family Elite Officer
Trebol ♣ (Ate the Sticky Fruit)
Child, I can't move! Please get this sticky fluid off me!
Time to make the contract.
Do not harm humans.
Obey the Family's orders.
What are you talking about?
Hey, what's wrong with my body?
Please put me back to-
Be quiet and get to work!
What? I can't speak!
Why can't I resist his commands?!
Obey the Family's orders.
Contract?!
Nobody remembers you anymore.
Even I've forgotten who you were.
You will work for Doffy or fight for him until you die!
What is going on?! I've been turned into a toy!
Exit through that door, and you'll be at the port.
Ah, a new worker! Your station will be...
Where am I?!
Don't drop the cargo!
...right here. Now, get to work!
I'm a pirate! This is just a bad dream. Wake up, me!
Get moving!
No, I don't want to work!
I refuse to spend the rest of my life working with these creepy toys!
So this was where they smuggled the weapons from?
But I can't resist them! I can't do anything!
I can't believe they had a port underground.
I have to contact the others...
Koala is waiting for my report!
Is there no way for me to move freely?!
I am the king of Prodence! Damn you, Doflamingo!
Will I be a toy for the rest of my life?
You can't be serious!
Somebody, help!
So they are Trebol and Sugar.
She really is a kid.
That's right.
She loves grapes. She's always eating them.
What about it?
That's essential to our plan.
Look at this!
This is a lump of the world's spiciest seasoning, tatababasco!
We've disguised it as a grape!
And you're giving that to Sugar?
I'm going to sneak it into her basket.
We've tested it on fifty Tontattans.
Every single one of them fainted, and twenty-eight nearly died!
You've tested it?
The plan is flawless! We just have to make her eat this.
Alright! Go, Leo!
I will watch over you!
That's so reassuring.
If a panic breaks out... I'm outta here.
Hang in there, Leo!
Yeah!
Be quiet, you guys!
Watch out for Trebol!
Be careful!
You're way too loud!
No problem.
All of you, prepare yourselves!
Once Sugar screams out...
all the toys in this country will turn back into big humans!
All the forgotten memories will come back!
With all his evil deeds exposed...
the pirate Doflamingo's...
true nature will be revealed!
I'm going. We will save our friends!
Yeah!
I'm telling you to be quiet!
We will reclaim King Riku's country!
Yeah!
Oh come on!
Shut up already!